export const Grammar2=[
  {
    question: "My brother knows how to fly an airplane. He … a pilot.",
    Options: ["is", "are", "am"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "My friend and I … both students at the same school.",
    Options: ["is", "are", "am"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Oh, no! ... I late for the final history exam?",
    Options: ["Am", "Are", "Is"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "My father and I... happy right now.",
    Options: ["Are", "Am", "Is"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "My Mathematics teacher ... really beautiful.",
    Options: ["Are", "Is", "Am"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "He is from Italy, she is from Spain, and Miko and Hiro ... from Japan.",
    Options: ["aren't", "are", "is"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Hello. It... nice to meet you.",
    Options: ["is", "am", "are"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "(A) How old ... you?\n(B) I... thirty years old)",
    Options: ["am/is", "are / are", "are / am"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "John and Holly... best friends.",
    Options: ["Are", "Is", "Am"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "I like my cousin, but he late. ... always",
    Options: ["are", "is", "aren't"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  }
]
